Oh. that's beautiful.
It was terrible. I can't do it.
Hmm. not yet.
But you will.
You're growing up so fast.
- You say that all the time.
- Yeah. it's because you are.
You look so much like your sister.
I wish I could remember her.
If I come back and you're a foot taller...
gonna ground you.
Shh.
Remember what we learned. okay?
Eve. come with me.
Stay quiet.
We opened our hearts to you.
We embraced you.
We let you. an outsider.
marry a daughter of our clan.
And how did you repay this kindness?
You took what was not rightfully yours.
And now. your wife is dead.
to atone for your transgressions.
Did you think that
you could just walk away?
Hmm?
Where is she?
Where is Eve?
Charming.
You're a fucking coward.
You're trying to convince yourself
that fate absolves you of your actions.
There are no choices.
Yeah. Does that make
what you do any easier?
It makes what I do...
necessary.
One bullet...
well placed...
can be a magical thing.
It's neither good...
nor evil.
But how a man uses it
reveals his true character.
You wanted choices.
Well. here they are.
You kill yourself.
and your daughter lives.
Or kill me.
and you and your daughter die together.
Choice is yours.
You've got your choice.
Now. do you have the balls to do it?
Papa!
Hey. baby. look at me.
- It's okay.
Come on.
Papa.
I'm sorry. honey.
- I never wanted this for you.
- Papa.
I'm sorry.
Papa!
Papa...
Tchaikovsky. How lovely.
At a time of loss.
there's nothing easier than pity
and nothing more difficult than the truth.
as there are no easy answers for grief.
I'd like to be honest with you.
Would that be all right?
Your father was a good man.
He wanted a free and open life for you.
Not like the one that he had to endure.
But we all live
with the decisions we make.
Now he's been taken from you.
I can do nothing about that.
But what I can do...
is offer to take you to his family.
They will look after you
and. hopefully...
one day become your family. too.
The Director will see you now.
Does she know who her parents really were?
Come here. Sit.
You dance. yes?
- Mm-hmm.
- I run this theater.
and I am always looking for new recruits.
I know you.
I know your pain.
What boils inside of you
under the surface.
I can give you somewhere
to put that anger.
Those men took your past.
Don't let them steal your future.
Well?
She says my path is now here
with the Ruska Roma.
Very well...
Eve.
Thank you. Mr. Winston.
You are most welcome. Miss MaCarro.
And know that I will
always be at your service.
My name is Nogi.
Did you know my father?
I did.
Your father was Ruska Roma. like me.
Like you will be. too.
He was what we call Kikimora.
What is that?
In Slavic mythology.
the Kikimora is a kind of spirit
to those with darkness in their hearts.
She can be vengeful and destructive.
Like the boogeyman?
Yes.
But to the innocent...
she can be a protector.
It is...
two sides...
to the one coin.
To kill...
to save.
But. ultimately...
it is up to you to choose.
Are you finished?
No.
Good.
That will be all for today.
Tend to your wounds before you get sepsis.
and we have to cut off your feet.
Tell Tatiana she's next.
"Her Majesty" says you're up.
That woman hates me.
She hates everybody.
Christ. Eve.
Why do you push yourself like this?
I want to be ready.
Ready for what?
You know what's funny?
When I was a little girl. I actually
did want to be a real ballerina.
You are a real ballerina.
You're the best dancer here.
That other shit.
you'll learn with training.
Fire!
One bullet.
well placed. can change the world.
The Kikimora's purpose is
to stop that bullet.
Time's up!
To become Kikimora
you must become the assassin.
You must learn to move like him
and think like him.
For this next exercise.
we will be using simulated rounds.
What are the rules?
Protect your ward at all costs.
That is the only rule.
Why did you fail?
He's too strong.
Do you really believe
that strength has anything to do
with whether you win or lose?
You will always be weaker.
You will always be smaller
and at a disadvantage.
He is beating you
because you are allowing him
to define the terms of the contest.
You want to win?
Change the terms.
Improvise. adapt. cheat.
Lean into your strengths.
not his.
Fight like a girl.
Begin.
Good.
Where is she?
Tatiana's things are gone.
Did something happen to her?
Sit.
Tatiana did not have
the qualities required
to continue with the Ruska Roma.
What are you talking about?
She lacked the killer instinct
I see in you.
Your childhood was taken.
This pain is what drives you.
Tatiana... there is sadness. not pain.
There's a difference.
You two are now on different paths.
Then why are you holding me back?
I'm ready.
Perhaps you are right.
It is time.
This is the final stage of your training.
Oh. my God.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I'm a fucking test?
How the mighty have fallen.
Do you know who I am?
No.
I'm you...
in ten fucking years.
Somehow you managed to get out.
but here you are back where you began.
All of this for what?
With this. Jardani.
your ticket is torn.
You can never come home again.
Take him to the lifeboat.
Do svidanya.
You're him.
The one they call the Baba Yaga.
The students all talk about you.
How do I get outta here?
The front door is unlocked.
No. I mean...
how do I start doing what you do?
Looks like you already have.
That door will lock sooner than you think.
You can still leave.
You still have a choice.
Why didn't you leave?
I'm working on it.
The Director feels you are ready
for your first contract.
You will protect this woman.
Katla Park.
Her father is our primary charge.
He is concerned that his competitors
may try to get to him
by ransoming his daughter.
Your job is to make sure
they don't get the chance.
To infiltrate past security.
you'll be using a modified
3D printed Glock 43X
with reinforced carbon fiber barrel.
and polymer rounds.
Rubber bullets?
Problem?
- No.
- You'll find Miss Park at Minus Eleven.
In position.
Copy.
I have the principal in sight.
Hold your position.
She can dance.
I got movement at ten o'clock.
A threat?
Stand by.
Hey!
Definitely a threat.
You should get out of the way.
I can't.
I understand.
Hey!
No. no. no.
I don't want anyone to touch me right now.
Hey. hey. It's okay.
You're safe now. it's fine.
Let's get you out of here.
Hey. what the hell
is goin' on up there?
Somebody respond.
Were you stuck in the elevator?
Yes. It was very scary.
Miss. something's leaking from your bag.
Yes. Thank you.
No problem.
Is there a reason
you've brought me a severed hand?
Look at the scar.
I've seen this before.
That's the same scar
as the man who murdered my father.
It was a mark from a tribe.
You knew who they were.
How dare you?
I have been protecting you.
Why didn't you tell me who they were?
My child. you do not understand.
People with that mark.
they have no rules.
no consequence. no mercy.
They do not interfere with our business.
and we do not interfere with theirs.
This is a pact as old as
the Ruska Roma itself.
All these rules. who are they serving?
When you deal in blood.
there must be rules...
- or nothing survives.
Why would a tribe try to kidnap a child?
I am warning you. you will not find them.
and hunting for them
will only bring chaos.
I'm ordering you. do not pursue this.
Do I make myself clear?
Please...
take your hand.
Welcome to the Continental.
Checking in?
No. I'd like to speak with the manager.
Is he expecting you?
No. he's not.
I see. And what. may I ask. is your name?
Eve. Eve MaCarro.
Let me see what I can do.
Eve MaCarro of the Ruska Roma.
What a pleasure to see you again.
Please.
So. what brings you here?
I'm looking for the tribe
that killed my father.
And if I suggested you didn't?
I would smile and nod and then ignore you.
Ah.
The Director has already
warned me about them and the rules.
So. I can appreciate your reluctance.
That's very kind of you.
but a few words of advice.
if I may. Miss MaCarro.
Whatever information
you think these people have.
it might not be
in your best interests to know it.
I still need to know.
"Needing to know" is what got us banished
from the Garden of Eden.
Are you prepared
to be cast out again. Eve?
Please.
Very well.
I'll give you this.
It's not a tribe. it's a cult.
That kills not just for business.
but for sport.
While we live among
so-called polite society. they do not.
Where can I find them?
The precise location is unknown.
But we do monitor them
when they stay at our hotels.
They have access to the Continentals?
Oh. yes. Better to have them
inside the tent. pissing out.
than outside. pissing in.
And. yes. there is a man
who bears that mark
staying at one of our hotels
at the present...
in Prague. I believe.
On what business?
Shall we?
Hello. my dear.
Muriel. be a darling
and bring up the latest
Blackwire submissions on a Daniel Pine.
Daniel Pine...
Contract submitted three days ago.
His bounty is set at two million.
He's currently holed up
inside the Prague Continental room 3-1-5.
No outside calls have been logged.
and he's purchased
a shitload of room service.
Mostly ice cream.
Sweet tooth. hmm?
Hard copy. please.
Sir...
there is a call for you.
From The Director.
- Checking in.
Certainly.
And how long will you be staying with us?
Just the night.
Room 314. please.
Still no movement
from Pine. What are my orders?
Keep your eyes on Pine.
We may have a taker.
You're right. We have a taker.
A woman. young. dark hair.
She's in.
Who are you?
Shit.
You're not supposed to say that word.
Right. Sorry.
- What's your name?
- Ella.
I'm Eve.
You're not here to hurt my daddy. are you?
Your father?
Ella. come here.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Why don't you come
stand behind me. sweetheart?
What do you want?
When I was a child.
men with your mark murdered my father.
I just want to know where to find them.
You have no idea
what you just walked into. do you?
No business being conducted.
They're just talking.
Contract services.
How can I help you?
Account 8-6-5-1.
Name on contract?
Daniel Pine.
Double the contract.
- Fuck.
You just made everything
a whole lot worse.
Those people that you're looking for?
They're surrounding this hotel right now.
hoping somebody breaks the rules
and takes the bait.
I think they were hoping that
somebody was gonna be you.
Now you've just made 'em antsy.
Why would they be at the hotel?
They just want me dead to get to her.
Baby. stay down!
Ella. come on.
Come on.
He's moving. Hallway.
Damn it!
Come on.
Back. back. back the other way. Go!
Wait. wait. Get behind me.
Come on.
Ella. honey...
let's go.
Why do they want her?
It's a cult.
No one gets out. Ever.
You gotta help me get Ella outta here.
She deserves a better life than this.
I can't. That's not why I'm here.
You're Kikimora.
Isn't that what you do?
Help me protect her.
I'll tell you where to find them.
Please?
Daddy...
are we going to die?
No. No. baby.
No. not today.
You can trust her.
- Hi.
- Huh?
It's okay.
Hey.
- How many left?
Two. Maybe ten.
- Oh. fuck it.
- Daddy!
Yes?
We have the girl.
Good.
Sir. there was someone else there.
Who?
A woman.
For the contract?
I don't think so.
I think she might have been after Ella.
Really?
Do we. uh...
Do we know who she is?
Not yet.
I left her for Continental security.
They started this.
That's bullshit.
I did not break any rules.
- You broke my fuckin' jaw.
- You're still using it.
I didn't kill anyone.
You're going to need to check out.
Understood.
And what will it be today. madam?
I'd like to go hunting.
Have you ever done business
with these people?
I have not.
But you know of them.
You know more than me. I assure you.
May I be "frank"?
Mm-hmm.
I prefer to keep it that way.
Hmm.
Are we just window-shopping today.
or would you like to make a purchase?
Depends on the merchandise.
After you. madam.
Pardon me.
So...
will this be a large or small game hunt?
Large.
The V Seven Harbinger TTI.
Thirty rounds of.308.
It's got a Trijicon AccuPoint
1-to-6 optical on top.
and in case you wanna get up close
and make it personal.
you've got a side RMR
for the faster. dirtier stuff.
TTI custom Benelli M2 21-inch fin grip.
Oversized charging handle.
oversized bolt release.
This will take a bear's head off. Easily.
Now. this is a personal favorite of mine.
- This...
Ah! Fuck! Bastards! Fuck!
Motherfuckers.
All right...
you didn't hear this from me.
Their precise location
has never been confirmed.
since anyone who's ever gone looking
has also gone missing.
That's bad math.
However. whispers suggest they've been
known to gather somewhere in these peaks.
deep in the mountains
past Abersee and Feldkirk.
It's not much.
It's more than I had.
Thank you.
Sorry about your shop.
I need a car.
Did you think I would not find out?
That you expressly disobeyed my orders?
Then tell me who they are.
I told you. we do not engage with them.
You risk the destruction of our family.
and for what?
Your own selfish reasons.
Return at once or I will have no choice.
Can I get you anything?
Just a coffee.
Come. let's go.
It's Agnetha!
Send somebody to the restaurant! Hurry!
Go around the back.
Don't let her escape!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- The fuck?
Chancellor. this is The Eye.
What is it?
The outsider has not been contained.
Engage full protocols.
Find her!
Ah. You're having a little tea party.
Aren't you going to say hello
to your grandfather?
Where is Daddy? Is he okay?
You have no idea. Ella. how worried I was.
All of us.
Your father...
well. he broke our customs.
He was trying to take you away.
Away from me.
Away from your family.
I hate you.
That hate will make you strong. Ella.
Chancellor.
We got her.
Is she dead?
She's Ruska Roma.
She has their mark.
You know. I met your Director once.
It was many years ago in Moscow.
Not a very pleasant lady.
But we did have a respectful conversation.
nonetheless.
A shared understanding
of the roles that we both play...
and. more importantly.
the roles that we don't play.
The Director didn't send me here.
The Ruska Roma
has nothing to do with this.
Well. it does now.
Why are you here?
If you've come for the girl.
you are gravely mistaken.
Ella is my granddaughter.
Someday. all of this will be hers.
My son...
well. he tried to deprive her
of her true heritage.
You put a contract on your own son?
You may have noticed we don't take well
to outsiders meddling in our town.
This is where people
like yourself come to live.
to have real lives.
To raise families.
Would you not like to someday
have a family of your own?
I had a family!
I was a child.
Men came into my house.
Men from your tribe.
Ah. I see.
This is about vengeance.
They killed my father
and tried to take me.
Tried to take you?
Fate is a very humbling thing.
What is it?
Well. she... she wasn't working for Pine.
She's here because I killed her father
when she was a child.
She's your sister.
No.
- For God's sake!
What are you doing?
Lena!
All this time. I thought you were dead.
What are you talkin' about?
You don't remember me. do you?
You were born here. Eve.
We both were.
My little sister has come home.
When I was younger. I used to wonder...
"Why did he take you and not me?"
I mean. later I realized
it was too late for me.
I'd already taken a life.
But you...
He thought he could raise you
with no memory of this place.
of your true home.
But I guess it never
leaves your blood. does it?
In the end.
we are who we are.
We are not the same.
Your people...
killed my father.
Our father. Yes. For betraying us.
And then our mother had to pay the price.
The Chancellor was trying
to save you that night.
He was trying to bring you back home.
as he would with anyone.
My father was trying
to give me a normal life!
Well. he would be very proud.
You're forcing children into this life!
As Ruska Roma has with you.
No! She gave me a choice! I chose this!
Oh. did you?
Or did fate just find
another path for you?
At least here we're honest
about who we are.
No Kikimora lies.
We've got eyes on her.
Cabin 83.
She's inside with Lena. sir. talking.
Take them out.
Sir?
Kill them both.
You heard The Chancellor. Blow it.
I was only nine
when they told us you were dead.
Save your breath.
I missed you.
Everyone. move in.
Check for survivors.
Strike team...
Strike team. do you copy?
Is it done?
This isn't done until you're dead.
Yes?
We have a problem. you and I.
And what problem might that be?
That a member of your tribe
has contravened a centuries old truce.
The Ruska Roma have no desire for a war.
Especially not with you.
Whether you sent her
or not is of no interest to me.
You will accept full consequences
of her actions.
- Which are?
- The end of your tribe.
Your students.
your fucking pets. everything.
Call her off.
Chancellor.
she's operating against Ruska Roma.
I could not call her off if I tried.
Then war it shall be.
Perhaps an agreement could be struck.
I can send someone to solve the problem.
Someone capable. No more bloodshed.
If you agree to this.
you must also agree
that your men will not engage.
If come midnight she still breathes.
retaliation will be inevitable and total.
And if the problem is taken care of?
Then I will reconsider my response.
Very well.
I will. of course. need your location.
A secret I assure you will die with me.
Madam. she is family.
She has made her choice.
The Baba Yaga.
Citizens of Hallstatt...
this order stays in effect
until the bells ring out.
As of now. you do not engage.
Anyone who feels compelled
to go against this order will be cast out.
Leave the wolf to its prey.
She sent you here to kill me?
That's up to you.
Or you can leave.
Your choice.
Do you remember me?
From the theater?
Remember what you said to me?
You told me I could leave.
that it was my choice.
It still is.
I'm not leaving.
You don't have to do this.
Just leave.
Leave.
Just... go.
He killed my father.
I know.
Let me finish this.
Midnight.
If it isn't done...
Rules.
And consequences.
Sir. he's let her go
and she's on the attack.
I recommend we re-engage full protocols.
Attention. Every citizen
is now being called to hunt the outsider.
Let's go.
Let's move. let's move!
Check the boathouse.
You see anything?
She's here!
Hurry up! With me. Be on alert.
Make sure everything is clear.
Cool.
Attention.
The outsider has entered the armory.
All teams proceed to the armory.
She wants me...
and she wants Ella.
Orders?
You find her...
and you destroy her.
Come on.
Keep your eyes open.
Two men down
at the armory entrance.
I repeat. two men down
Hold there. Hold.
- Go! Go!
Requesting all citizens
to the tunnels immediately.
All citizens proceed to the tunnels.
Move in. I got your six.
Oh. shit.
- Over there!
Go. go!
She's there!
We have
lost sight of the outsider.
All teams be on alert.
Continue to patrol the perimeter.
We're on the square.
Eye. report back. Report back.
Alpha Team. halt!
She has exited the tunnels.
Check behind you.
Sir.
In the interest of Hallstatt's survival.
it would be best to relocate you.
In 200 years. no leader of Hallstatt
has ever left the seat of power
to seek shelter.
I understand.
But. sir. we've also
lost track of John Wick.
Let go!
Let go of me.
Attention.
Requesting all citizens...
This is suicide.
It's fucking John Wick.
Come on. He's only one man.
Cut across here.
Don't you think we've had enough?
Do you really think
you're going to save her from me?
From... From all of this?
Whatever happens here...
nothing is going to change.
The village will remain.
the children will be raised.
and the system will continue as it has
for the last thousand years.
Look at you.
You know that you don't choose
to be a killer. you are chosen.
Just like your sister was chosen.
Just like Ella has been chosen.
It is your fate and you cannot change it.
The only person
you're fighting is yourself--
It's okay.
Let's go.
Hmm?
Jardani?
So. she is dead?
He is dead.
Fine.
Daddy?
Hey. sweetie.
Come here.
Get up here.
Room 814.
I trust the talk went well?
Checking in. hmm?
Yes.
Safe haven. Miss MaCarro.
You may have cut the snake's head.
but the body still lives.
They'll be looking for you.
Contract services. How may I help you?
Name on the account?
Processing.
♪ One step closer and you're all mine ♪
♪ You leave me no choice ♪
♪ Burned into mind ♪
♪ I'm going in for the kill ♪
♪ There is no other way out ♪
♪ If you need to. baby ♪
♪ Cry. cry about it ♪
♪ Why don't you cry? ♪
♪ Time to pay for what you started ♪
♪ Who's sorry now? ♪
♪ Tell your lies
Yeah. you can run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight like a girl? ♪
♪ Fight like a girl ♪
♪ And take this world ♪
♪ Tonight. you're the victim ♪
♪ Of your own crime ♪
♪ You made your choice ♪
♪ You'll swallow your fate ♪
♪ Stone cold ♪
♪ Feed the snakes ♪
♪ Hold that fire. say my name ♪
♪ Baby. you can cry ♪
♪ Cry. cry about it ♪
♪ Why don't you cry? ♪
♪ Time to pay for what you started ♪
♪ Who's sorry now? ♪
♪ Tell your lies ♪
♪ Yeah. you can run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight like a girl? ♪
♪ Fight like a girl ♪
♪ Sinner and savior
I've been walking the line ♪
♪ Killers collide
The feeling. an adrenaline high ♪
♪ Violent behavior in my blood ♪
♪ No one but myself to trust ♪
♪ Vengeance. well
That shit's a hell of a drug ♪
♪ Break the cycle. I don't wanna ♪
♪ Break your spinal. yeah. I'm gonna ♪
♪ My finger on the trigger
I've been feeding the pain ♪
♪ You'll never fight like a girl
So I keep winning the game ♪
♪ I wanna see you cry ♪
♪ Cry. cry about it ♪
♪ Why don't you cry? ♪
♪ Time to pay for what you started ♪
♪ Who's sorry now? Tell your lies ♪
♪ Yeah. you can run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight like a girl? ♪
♪ Sinner and savior
I've been walking the line ♪
♪ Devil disguised
I see it when I look in your eyes ♪
♪ Yeah. you can run your mouth ♪
♪ But can you fight like a girl? ♪
♪ Fight like a girl ♪
♪ I know I should have the pride ♪
♪ I know I should have the spirit ♪
♪ I know you would tell a lie ♪
♪ If you knew I couldn't hear it ♪
♪ You'd say it. oh. so proudly ♪
♪ But do you know your crimes? ♪
♪ And do you think about me? ♪
♪ And were you ever mine? ♪
♪ You say I mean the world to you ♪
♪ To keep me on my knees ♪
♪ Then dig the knife in deeper ♪
♪ Just to watch how much I bleed ♪
♪ I'm stripped to the bone
I don't want to be alone ♪
♪ No matter how I plead ♪
♪ You do it 'cause you know you can ♪
♪ Turn around
And bite the hand that feeds ♪
♪ Every promise that you break ♪
♪ Every time you try
To place the blame on me ♪
♪ I don't want to control the pain ♪
♪ Turn it into the fire I need ♪
♪ The feeling rushes through me ♪
♪ Can you still hear me cry? ♪
♪ But after all I'm standing ♪
♪ On my own this time ♪
♪ You say I mean the world to you ♪
♪ To keep me on my knees ♪
♪ Keep me on my knees ♪
♪ Then dig the knife in deeper ♪
♪ Just to watch how much I bleed ♪
♪ I'm stripped to the bone
I don't want to be alone ♪
♪ No matter how I plead ♪
♪ You do it 'cause you know you can ♪
♪ Turn around
And bite the hand that feeds ♪
♪ I played your twisted game ♪
♪ Played your twisted game ♪
♪ Now watch me walk through the flames ♪
♪ Choking on the taste of your mistakes ♪
♪ And now you're the one on your knees ♪
♪ That's why
You bite the hand that feeds ♪